※2017.05.03追記:
前回のモーションでカクカクしているとの指摘があったので、いろいろと手を加えてみました。
しかし、依然として下手かも知れませんので大目に見ていただけると嬉しいです。(笑)

高垣楓が、「こいかぜ」をアイマスOFAで踊るモーションです。

ご利用の際、腕捩り・手捩りのボーンが必須ですのでご注意ください。

改変・再配布はご自由ですが、版権のあるゲームのモーションなので、
ご利用にはご注意をしたほうがいいと思います。

This MMD motion is the one from Idolm@ster One For All,
where Kaede Takagaki performs the song Koikaze.

"Arm Twist" and "Wrist Twist" bones are necessary for a model to use this motion data.

The MMD data is free to modify and redistribute,
but keep in mind that the eitire work is originated from a copyrighted game.